Welcome back.
Alright, let's try and figure out some more clues here.
In fact, one thing I want to do is click on these things again.
You found me.
I mean, that one has to be correct, right?
So it's the lying down thing.
I would say this one is not fine then.
I don't know what that is.
Let's just go question mark.
Yeah, very unsure.
This one has to be fine, right?
You found me.
What else could it be?
You... question mark me.
Oh, wait, did I get it wrong before?
This is follow!
What the hell am I doing?
You follow... follow me.
Then kit went off.
But obviously that could also mean you find me.
But it would make sense for the kit to say you follow me when I found him, right?
So if that means follow, do I have anything like that in the book that I can fill out?
This is like, no access granted.
Okay.
Go back up.
You must need go door.
I think need sounds more likely here.
For sure.
And then the kit set this over here.
You found me.
And then he says, you follow me.
He's also doing the hand motion, right?
So yeah, for sure follow.
Now this dude, no clue.
I have no idea what's going on over there.
I want to see if there's more to be found over here again.
Maybe here?
Right.
What did you say here?
Yeah, you follow me.
Good.
Beautiful background.
Look at that.
Really nice.
And I'm definitely in the city being depicted in those murals.
Okay, let's head inside here once again.
Okay.
Now I wonder if there's anything else I can do here.
Can I maybe sneak off to somewhere else?
Doesn't look like it.
Grab a piece of rock.
Throw it.
Get it!
And off I go.
Sneaky, sneaky, sneaky.
Very good.
Now, what did you say here?
You and me gotta go to the temple city.
The devotee closed the door.
You, me, we follow the key?
See, now I'm confused.
That's why I put find here last time, I think.
Maybe it's look for a key.
Maybe the kid is saying, you look for me.
Or come with me.
We...
No, that doesn't make sense.
You, me, follow key?
What?
That is not congruent with what the kid was saying before.
We find key.
That makes the most sense.
That's why I put find here.
That is breaking my mind right now.
Completely.
Well, we're pretty sure this is a key.
What else could it be, right?
We gotta go to the city.
The devotee closed the door, so therefore we need to find a key.
And he was looking for the key, right?
We look for a key, but we also have a word for look already, right?
Which is the eye, which is seeing.
So it's not look.
What else could be a word for follow?
You come with me?
You mean come key?
No.
We find key.
We search key.
Oh, you search for me.
Maybe that's what the kid was saying.
Search.
Which means it's that one.
Searching.
Yes!
That makes sense.
Go slash pass.
OK.
Seek want.
OK, that's not what I thought, but OK.
Find.
Yeah, good.
Wonderful.
Right.
You me must go to the temple city.
They close the door.
We want key.
We want to seek the key, right?
Got it.
Seek slash want.
Interesting.
OK.
That's nice.
So now we got a couple left here.
This guy I'm very unsure of.
I have nothing that immediately says stop, you know?
So I'm not going to try and guess that.
Man, what a nice feeling it is to unlock this.
Reminds me a little bit of Return of the Obra Dinn when you finally get the right guesses, you know, and it all clicks into place.
It's the same sort of feeling you get.
You find key.
We ascend the stairs.
Although the way he's holding up his arms like that almost makes it seem like he's praising the sun.
Praise the sun!
Three words, right?
All right.
Let's go up.
OK.
So you know what?
I just had a thought, actually.
We did read that the church could help us with the puzzle in the cemetery, right?
But perhaps the cemetery is also a clue as to what we need to do in the church.
Cemetery was this way.
Let me have another look at that place.
Not to mention what's going on in here.
We got to see that again.
Very weird.
And it's like hidden off and the ambiance is here.
It's super creepy too.
I'm putting my hand on the thing.
What is happening?
So this is referring to the city.
Oh, wait a minute.
Does this mean I am currently in the lowest parts of the city?
It's like saying, hey, you are here.
But what about these dots moving around?
That's weird.
And the TIE fighter.
When I click on this, then it just sort of closes.
Oh, you know what I think this is?
Maybe this is a fast travel system for later.
Think about it.
Right?
Because otherwise it would be a pain.
Has to be like that.
Then again, what are the dots all about and what about the video conferencing?
Okay, let's have another look here.
So, in the church we had four different places we could do things at.
Which makes sense with the four different statues here.
Also, why is this cat so occupied with... what's going on over here?
Okay, so here we have music.
I want to say water slash vase.
Sword.
Sword and key.
Okay, so here we have preacher, a human, and a devotee.
Right?
And this one says God sees us.
Yeah, God sees us.
God sees us.
Now, we also had different statues like this where it said God protects us or embraces us.
Did I get that one right, by the way?
Oh, it was love, right?
Yeah, so God loves us.
God sees us.
Maybe those are the ones I need to focus on.
Let me see this one again.
You're seeking God?
The church will help you.
I mean, of course.
That makes sense.
I'm trying to understand the implication of these different symbols over here.
The key, the sword, the vase, and what was the last one?
Music, right.
Key, sword, vase, and music.
Hmm.
Let's go back to the church.
I'm trying to remember if there were other areas that I could have gone to that I didn't go to yet.
Let's do a quick backtrack through some of these regions.
I need to get out of the...
No, I need to go to the garden.
And then from here, I want to quickly speak to this guy.
So now that I have all this knowledge, you're gonna say the preacher...
Hmm.
Something garden.
We must need fine preacher.
I need...
The preacher needs the garden.
I need to find preacher.
Plants are dying.
God damn, man.
Hmm.
I need to love the plants.
What does that even mean?
I cannot figure out what that must slash need is supposed to be.
Okay, there's nothing over here.
Except it does look like something can be done over there in the corner.
Guess not.
In this spot, there's gotta be a place I haven't gone, right?
This is God loves us.
Oh, talks to us, right.
Makes sense with the open mouth.
So we have God loves us.
God talks to us.
God sees us.
Do we have a fourth one?
Oh my God, there's stuff up here too.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Oh, I need to rearrange these beds or carts so I can get up there.
What's this?
Oh, is that a coin?
Oh, it's a coin.
Move that over there.
Then we're gonna take this guy
and move him.
Oh, I can only move them in one direction.
Oh, okay, I see.
So let's move this guy out of the way.
And that guy.
Ah, well, we gotta move this guy first to here.
Get this guy out of the way.
Ah, but then I can't put the other guy back.
Damn.
Ah, I see, I see.
Do that.
Move this guy all the way out of the way here.
Like that.
Go back over here now and push these two in.
What is this place even?
How come I don't speak the language of these people?
That's the real question here.
Oh, well, wait, we have an issue here now.
Oh, no.
Oh.
This is not gonna work.
Shit.
How the hell am I gonna do that?
Oh, I moved this all the way over there, perhaps.
Ah, but wait a second.
Move this guy over here.
Grab this dude.
Drag him over there.
Get this guy out of the way to here.
And we take this bed.
They look like beds to me, but they're carts.
Drag him over here.
Wonderful.
Now we take this guy and put him back.
This is a tricky puzzle here.
Now we take these two guys, move them like this.
There we go.
What a nice little puzzle.
And now we can move these guys back.
Must be a hard work out here in the sun, huh?
The sun that kills.
Oh, there.
This guy over here now.
And now we can move this dude.
Also, I thought maybe I could go up these ladders and go in here, but not really the case, huh?
Yay!
A coin!
Yes!
I knew it.
Ooh.
God loves men.
Devotees seek God.
What about women?
Does she not like women?
Devotees seek God.
What a shiny coin.
Look at that.
Nice.
Alrighty.
Let's go this way.
Now we know who to give the coin to.
Musical instruments.
Yo!
This has to mean music.
Plural.
Musics.
Or musical instruments.
Yeah.
Hey buddy.
Greetings.
I sell musical instruments.
You like music?
Sell.
100%.
And this guy is...
instruments.
Hello.
I sell instruments.
You like music?
I do like music.
In fact, I'm liking this music right now.
You're selling potions.
What the hell?
Look at this.
It's like helping symbol.
Hand-to-hand combat.
No, not hand-to-hand combat.
Hand-to-hand helping.
Potions.
Potion.
That's totally a potion.
And then we have keys.
Incidentally, all the different things we saw on the rotating pillar in the cemetery.
And look at this.
Pottery.
It's a vay slash pot.
Key, keys.
And pots.
Pot.
Perfect.
Hey buddy.
So you're saying I sell pots.
You want pots?
I'm good.
Thanks.
This is going to be so easy.
Watch.
Music.
Pots is that one.
This is the music you hear.
What?
Did I get that wrong?
How is this wrong?
Pot.
Unless it's reversed.
I would say this is music, that's instrument.
It's not the other way around, is it?
Instrument?
Okay, never mind.
I guess I got it wrong.
Um...
Interesting.
Pots.
Keys.
Potions.
And instruments.
Wait, how is that wrong?
I don't get it.
Pots.
Pottery.
A hundred percent.
Instrument.
And this.
Sound.
Music.
I guess I'm wrong about this.
Perhaps I don't know what this is.
But it's the same symbol for music as here, you know?
Okay, well, these two are definitely confirmed.
This one I'm unsure about.
Let's keep going.
This is where I came from.
Let's head up to... Let me see what you were saying actually again.
Hello, I sell instruments.
You like music?
It's totally what he's saying.
What else could he be saying?
You love... you like...
um...
melodies?
It wouldn't change the fact that it's still the symbol for me.
Hold on.
There's no way.
How is that not correct?
Okay.
Weird.
I am so sure of that.
It kind of boggles my mind that that isn't correct.
I can't wait to see what it actually is.
Let's go give that coin to the beggar.
Which I believe is... Oh, I forgot.
Is it up here?
Kinda.
Yeah, we can go this way.
And then head towards the church.
Um, yeah.
Look what I got for you.
Also, let me quickly take a look at this again before I give it over.
God loves men.
Devotees seek God.
Here you go, buddy.
You, man-human, temple city, I like you.
I like you too.
You, human, temple city?
What?
Is he asking me, are you a devotee?
As in, you know, a human that is affiliated with the temple, aka God.
Weird.
You human...
Oh, that is tough.
I don't know what that means.
Okay.
Oh.
I mean, yeah, I know that.
That's a key.
So we've got a half-full pot.
A full pot.
And a pot filled in various locations.
Or something.
Huh?
This is the key.
Maybe it's the size of it.
Small pot, medium pot, or big pot.
Small, medium, big.
Small pot.
You're seeking the preacher.
Go to the garden.
Preacher loves the garden.
Okay.
All right.
And you're saying that specific pot is the key, huh?
Uh...
Come on.
This guy is saying I love music.
It's gotta be.
He's vibing to it.
Okay, fine.
Let's set up and go to the garden.
Down here.
Okay.
So garden is up here.
We gotta look for a pot that is shaped like the thing on the thing.
Okay.
That one?
Oh, I guess it's not a small one.
We need to find a smaller version of that pattern and shape.
I would say this one is too big.
Do we have a very small one?
Um...
Not really.
Let me see what you're saying now.
Plants are dying.
Yeah, yeah.
How is that not a small one?
Hmm.
One, two, three stripes on it.
One, two, three.
But that one didn't work.
Well, they're smaller ones.
Let's just try that one.
Nothing in that one.
Well, we also have this guy over here.
You find something?
Oh!
A key!
And you know what?
It kind of makes sense that I would have to look through a couple because... I mean, there are different pots in here, right?
All I know is that it looks like the one in the picture.
Okay, now I got a key.
Is that gonna unlock something in the church?
Can I go up here?
Oh yeah, I can, of course.
Ah!
Of course!
Let's see what we have here.
Oh man, I fucking love video games.
I love the look of this room.
I love the way the sun shines through the window.
I love the ambiance.
I'm seeing all these things I can click on.
I just get happy.
I'm so happy.
Let's see what this is.
Got a shovel and a lot of text here.
Me find... Oh, I think I may know what that means, actually.
I find you.
You find... No, not you.
I find something.
That finds God.
I'm going to the cemetery.
And I go to the temple city.
Hmm.
The preacher.
Okay.
Ah, but check this out.
I know what some of this means.
That one means C slash look.
You see that?
This is like a... something with look or see.
This looks like a lens.
Telescope?
I find telescope.
Telescope finds God.
I'm going to the cemetery.
I gotta go through temple city.
Hmm.
I got temple city wrong for sure.
I'm gonna say this looks like I don't know, looking glass or telescope.
Maybe just lens.
Let's go telescope for now.
Let's see that one.
Okay.
Yeah.
That is definitely a lens.
Maybe the lens can be put in a specific spot, and it will guide the sunlight in to point to somewhere specific.
Right.
I find telescope.
Telescope finds God.
Maybe he says I found the telescope.
Because it's there on the... let's actually call it lens.
I found the lens.
The lens will find God.
I'm going to the cemetery, and then I pass through temple city or something.
Although temple city... still not quite sure what that means.
Where are you passing through?
Hmm.
Well, I got it written down now.
Okay.
Key.
We know that one.
Where is that?
Key.
Potion.
Where's my potion?
Lens.
And this is a vase or vase?
Or pot?
Oh.
Maybe I got that one wrong.
No fucking way.
Okay.
A pot.
Good.
A key.
A lens.
Nice.
And a potion.
Holy shit.
I nailed all four.
Alright.
But here comes the big question.
What the hell is this then?
Can I double use these?
I can't.
Okay.
Is this this?
I mean, this is for sure music.
Temple slash... could have gotten that wrong.
Why did I think temple city?
I gotta go back and figure out the first clue I got with that.
Potions.
Yeah, that makes so much sense.
Let's take another look here.
So obviously the preacher went out with a shovel.
Dug up the lens.
He's trying to find God with it.
What if the beggar is the preacher?
And he's just hoping someone passes him by, you know, hands over a coin.
And you know, leads him on his original mission.
Probably not though.
What's up here?
Right.
Okay.
What is this over here?
Oh, we got a little path?
Look at that!
Yo!
Oh,
interesting.
No way, right?
I was about to say that doesn't fit at all.
Okay.
Very ominous atmosphere in here.
Where is this lead though?
So we need some kind of thing that can be slotted in there.
Let's go up this way.
Hey man, thanks for the assist.
You're seeking the preacher.
Go to the garden.
Preacher loves the garden.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got it already.
Let's go back in here.
Perhaps that lens will fit into the sockets that we saw in here.
I doubt it though.
Because those sockets were rectangular.
But who knows?
Okay, here it is.
Oh, it totally has to be its round.
Yes!
Okay.
So this symbol means what?
Devotee.
Wait a minute.
Oh no, wait, wait, what?
It means different things.
Oh!
The man looks at the devotee.
Okay.
Why does the man look at the devotee?
Why do you want to look at the devotee?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Go over here, go over here.
Put it in.
Oh, this is so satisfying.
Devotee looks at God.
Who watches the watcher?
Okay, now we head over to the other side.
Man, this is great.
Man looks at devotee.
Devotee looks at God.
Who does God look at?
That symbol.
God looks at...
Oh, what's it going to be?
Let me think, who could it be?
The sun, maybe.
Before I do it, music?
God looks at instruments?
Oh, that's interesting.
What's up with that?
And here?
Cross.
Who does the preacher look at?
Men.
He talks to the man.
The preacher talks to the man.
God looks at instruments.
Men look at devotees.
And devotees look at God.
Weird.
So what am I noting down here?
Oh, I'm noting down what I just found.
The man looks at the devotee.
Devotee looks at God.
The preacher talks to the man.
And God sees slash looks instruments.
Okay, that's weird.
Maybe music is the overall sort of driving force in this world.
Something higher than God itself.
Very interesting.
Okay, let's head back out.
Now, what did this guy say again?
I need to quickly check something.
I found the lens.
Lens found God.
I'm going to the cemetery.
I'm passing through a certain part.
I think the temple slash city here, whatever that symbol is, this symbol, refers to a part of the city.
He's passing through that part of the city.
I got to go back to the very beginning where I found the temple slash city symbol and figure out what it actually means.
Question is, which direction do I go?
It's all a bit convoluted here.
I want to go back to the cemetery.
Oh, I get it now.
It just dawned on me.
I get it.
I understand.
God looks at music.
Yeah, I see now.
And the God is the guy in the center, right?
So the musical instrument needs to point to that.
Ah, that's so smart.
That's beautiful.
That's really cool.
So God looks at instruments.
Instruments need to be pointing that way.
Ah, that's so smart.
The only thing is devotees, what could they be referred to here?
What I mean is man could be represented by Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Key, sword, and vase.
Or pot, I mean.
So we have devotee, man,
and instruments.
God.
Could God be represented?
Ah, man, that's a tough one.
I don't know what these things correspond to.
Do you know what I mean?
Is the key supposed to represent man or what?
This thing is breaking my mind.
Oh, also we have this.
I mean, we only have a couple left here, it seems.
Oh, I get it.
Selling.
The guy's like, no, no, I want five pounds for this.
That's totally selling.
Then we have this.
Temple, city, music, fly, up ascent climb.
I don't want to brute force this, even though I totally could at this point.
I want to see the clues again.
I think if I can solve the book right now, it will provide some kind of assistance for the cemetery.
Now, I never remember which way to go just back out.
Is it just here?
Okay, good.
This place took me to the plants, I think.
I want to go out.
And I think I want to get caught here.
Let me also see this again.
Yumi, must need go pass.
Uh...
Hmm.
Where are we going through?
Let's seek the key.
Nobody says that in that way.
That's such a weird thing to say.
You say, let's find the key.
You found the key!
Yumi, up ascent climb.
Maybe we go onwards.
Continue.
Escape!
Hmm.
Uh,
let's just get caught here.
Hello!
Take me out.
Uh, that's fine.
Yep.
Bag out here.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to see this conversation again down here.
And you said... Oh, you found me.
Right.
But you were about to say something else.
I must...
go up.
I'm going to the abbey.
Bye.
So what does this mean?
I must slash need up ascent climb.
You know what?
I think I'm confusing my... I think I got these completely wrong.
Let's just remove this entirely because it's warping my thinking.
It's making me think it's something to do with that when it probably isn't.
Yeah, this one has to be music.
This one could be barter, actually.
Barter.
So what could the kid be saying?
I...
must go?
Is it simply, I gotta go?
Let's head back down here.
I think this is where I first found the symbol for Temple slash City.
Yeah, it's this guy right here.
God damn it.
Devotee seeking God.
And then something...
God... Devotee seeking God atop in the heavens.
Could it mean heaven?
He's up in the heaven, right?
In heaven?
You know, this actually looks a lot like the Tower of Babel.
You know how you have these layers here?
Looks exactly like the illustrations that you usually see with the Tower of Babel.
Not to mention the whole language thing, right?
Different cultures and levels of the tower.
And of course, God.
Is that where we're going with this?
Does this mean tower?
But what is this?
Maybe this is like...
handiwork or craftsmanship.
The act of crafting something.
Well...
I don't know.
The crystal ball is...
foggy on this one.
I like this music down there.
I want it to play more often.
Now, you guys were saying also something with the Temple City, right?
Yeah.
Okay, so this is a simple two word sentence.
God...
What?
Maybe he's saying God's above.
We seek to pass through above.
Help us.
What could that mean?
God...
God... God what?
God exists?
You want to go up to God.
You seek God, I understand.
You seek to pass through whatever this is.
A gate.
Wait, could it simply mean gate of God?
I want to go through the gate of God?
I mean, we have door.
Maybe there's also a gate.
This is a mystery for the ages.
Yeah.
You're saying the same thing, right?
Warrior, warrior.
The warriors
denies devotees.
Warriors lock the door.
What does this simple mean?
Warrior, warrior.
Something.
What a mystery!
He's also saying he's going through this... whatever that is.
The preacher.
Potion, lens, pot, and key.
Maybe we can find a symbol with the line and the circle somewhere else.
Give us a hint here.
Line and circle.
The closest thing is this, but not really it.
This one, no clue.
I think I got these two correct.
How is this not pottery?
Am I losing my mind?
Maybe I missed an area where there's a clue to this.
What was down... what's over here?
Oh!
What the hell is this?
Oh my god.
Another one of these.
A line.
Oh!
It totally is a fast travel.
You helped me.
Plants are dying.
Me seek want plant death dead?
Huh?
What do I... do I write something?
Wait, what?
I'm so confused.
So he's contacting someone else on Zoom.
I cannot type... I'm trying to type something.
That doesn't work.
You helped me.
What?
I've got zero clue...
at what is going on.
I may...
I've missed something with this dude over here.
What's going on with this?
I don't get it at all.
Is it just whoever gets the higher status?
So for example... okay, actually, wait a minute.
Human.
He got God, so he's going to get a point.
Oh!
I see.
It's just pure RNG.
Okay, I got Preacher.
Oh, no, I got Devotee.
He got Warrior, so he has higher than me.
I see.
I got Warrior.
You got God... are you kidding me?
I lost.
Maybe I have to win.
I guess we try that one.
Shit.
Actually, it's pretty good.
Yeah, I win.
Let's see another one.
Ah, shit.
That means I automatically lose, actually.
Yeah, very unlucky.
Now, there's no way it's the same now, right?
This is God now.
Shit, Devotee.
Ah!
But you got a human.
I win.
Humans are trash.
Give me God.
Okay, I'll take that.
Yeah!
Give me that ball.
I win.
Okay.
So that's all that is?
I thought maybe if I won in a convincing manner, he would open a door for me or something.
Let's head down here now.
I guess I cannot enter here, so let me go back inside of there.
Yeah, I'm not...
sure what to do right now.
I'm going to take one of these stones.
Get it, sucker!
Hop through the door.
I hate this simple.
I hate this simple so much.
You, me, us, we.
It must mean must.
I cannot see another way.
This one, though, you, me, pass...
Where?
Pass what?
Where are we going?
Where are
we going, kid?
What does this mean?
Also, I cannot believe this puzzle right here.
This is breaking my mind.
Maybe saying we must toil to go past somewhere.
And this is toiling at work?
We must work our way up?
Wait.
Work our way up!
Wait a minute.
We must work our way up.
Or maybe undetected.
No.
Backdoor?
We must go through backdoor.
Is that what that means?
Backdoor.
Because the devotees closed the main door.
Up?
Maybe work?
It doesn't work.
Well, shit, I have no idea.
God, I feel so stupid.
You, me, what?
We did it?
We won?
We... What do we do?
We found the key.
We are the best?
He's throwing up his arms, right?
Yay, we did it!
We rock!
Shit,
I don't know.
You and me.
Ah, I don't know.
I give up on that.
We're gonna go on.
I cannot figure this out.
Where do I wanna go?
Maybe back to cemetery.
I feel like that's the biggest sort of area we haven't really...
Oh, let me try this thing now that I did the other one.
See if anything's changed here.
Okay, there's five dots, whatever that means.
Here we have no connection.
Oh, look now.
Fast travel?
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
I knew it.
But what is going on with this?
That's the real mystery here.
I...
What word could possibly work there?
I work.
I want plants...
dead.
What?
I seek...
looking for dead plants.
I want plants to die.
Huh?
I...
nourish dying plants.
I water.
I...
Okay, so we obviously need to have seek slash want in there.
So I something want dead plants.
And why is this one blinking?
I
don't understand.
Is there another place we haven't gone?
At this point I'm trying to think maybe we missed something somewhere.
Either that or...
I'm actually just monumentally stupid.
Because I cannot figure this out.
Let's go back to the very beginning here.
I gotta see if I missed something.
All the way over here.
Can I open a door here maybe?
What if I go down there again?
For sure not this way.
Okay, let's have a look at this.
Plants are dying.
Sun is shining.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We get it.
And over here...
God speaks to us.
Yeah, God speaking to men.
And we get infused with knowledge.
We become devotees.
Because of that.
You know, the sun nourishes us.
Therefore we praise the sun.
Right.
The big problem though is this drawing over here.
This right here.
Oh wait, where is it?
Is it further up?
Oh yeah, it's somewhere further up.
It's the one with the line and the circle on it.
This one.
God, I hate this symbol so much.
Devotees seeking God above.
Right.
It's gotta be above.
Not necessarily I guess, but who knows.
Barter.
Oh, you know what?
Wait a sec.
Barter.
If that's Barter...
Why did I put this guy here?
Why have we seen this symbol?
This is Climb.
Barter.
For sure Barter.
Right.
Now I forgot where exactly I saw this.
But you know.
Above.
Devotees seeking God.
Oh, this is rough.
I just don't know.
Where
is the clue that I need?
Um, surely nothing there.
You know what?
Let me take a look at this journal again, but the later pages.
Migo.
I feel like it means ascend.
Right?
Because the devotees were looking for God.
They found God.
So they had to ascend the city, right?
To get to God.
Every time you go one level in the city slash tower, you get closer to God.
But if he's going to the cemetery.
And from there he's going above.
Does that make sense?
Maybe he means he's passing on because he's going to the cemetery.
But that would imply that we need a death or death glyph.
And we don't have that here.
The man looks at the devotee.
The preacher talks to the man.
The devotee looks at God.
And God sees the instruments.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I mean, I can try one thing here.
I just realized the solution to the puzzle there, actually.
Now, I may not have the solution to my book and the remaining words.
But I think I can solve the cemetery puzzle now.
I get it.
For some reason I thought I had to sort of angle the statues towards the different facing sides of the bottom left statue.
So therefore I had to find the link between the key and the other symbols there with devotees, men and preacher.
But that is actually not what I need to do.
They just need to look at each other.
That's the whole point.
Can't believe it took me that long.
Graveyard is here.
In fact, let's save that for next episode.
I'm going to take a quick break.
I'll see you then.
Bye-bye.